//create the quiz questions
let questions = [
      {
        question: "1) Why is AWS more economical than traditional data centers for applications with varying compute workloads?",
        choiceA: "Amazon EC2 costs are billed on a monthly basis",
        choiceB: "Users retain full administrative access to their Amazon EC2 instances.",
        choiceC: "Amazon EC2 instances can be launched on demand when needed",
        choiceD: "Users can permanently run enough instances to handle peak workloads.",
        correct: "C)",
      },
      {
        question: "2) Which AWS service would simplify the migration of a database to AWS?",
        choiceA: "AWS Storage Gateway",
        choiceB: "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)",
        choiceC: "Amazon EC2",
        choiceD: "Amazon AppStream 2.0",
        correct: "B)",
      },
      {
        question: "3) Which AWS offering enables users to find, buy, and immediately start using software solutions in their AWS environment?",
        choiceA: "AWS Config",
        choiceB: "AWS OpsWorks",
        choiceC: "AWS SDK",
        choiceD: "AWS Marketplace",
        correct: "D)",
      },
      {
        question:"4) Which AWS networking service enables a company to create a virtual network within AWS?",
        choiceA: "AWS Config",
        choiceB: "Amazon Route 53",
        choiceC: "AWS Direct Connect",
        choiceD: "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC)",
        correct: "D)",
      },
      {
        question: "5) Which of the following is an AWS responsibility under the AWS shared responsibility model?",
        choiceA: "Configuring third-party applications",
        choiceB: "Maintaining physical hardware",
        choiceC: "Securing application access and data",
        choiceD: "Managing guest operating systems",
        correct: "B)",
      },
      {
        question: "6) Which component of the AWS global infrastructure does Amazon CloudFront use to ensure low-latency delivery?",
        choiceA: "AWS Regions",
        choiceB: "Edge locations",
        choiceC: "Availability Zones",
        choiceD: "Virtual Private Cloud (VPC)",
        correct: "B)",
      },
      {
        question: "7) How would a system administrator add an additional layer of login security to a user's AWS Management Console?",
        choiceA: "Use Amazon Cloud Directory",
        choiceB: "Audit AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) roles",
        choiceC: "Enable multi-factor authentication",
        choiceD: "Enable AWS CloudTrail",
        correct: "C)",
      },
      {
        question: "8) Which service can identify the user that made the API call when an Amazon EC2 instance is terminated?",
        choiceA: "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        choiceB: "AWS CloudTrail",
        choiceC: "AWS X-Ray",
        choiceD: "AWS Identity and Access Management (AWS IAM)",
        correct: "B)",
      },
      {
        question: "9) Which service would be used to send alerts based on Amazon CloudWatch alarms?",
        choiceA: "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)",
        choiceB: "AWS CloudTrail",
        choiceC: "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        choiceD: "Amazon Route 53",
        correct: "A)",
      },
      {
        question: "10) Where can a user find information about prohibited actions on the AWS infrastructure?",
        choiceA: "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        choiceB: "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
        choiceC: "AWS Billing Console",
        choiceD: "AWS Acceptable Use Policy",
        correct: "D)",
      },
];